Kyoka?
쿄카…
Now we have the brain that controls the Red Strings.
이제 레드 스트링스를 조종할 수 있는 대뇌를 얻었어
I'm sorry, Kasane.
미안해, 카사네…
I think they are here to welcome us.
우리를 환영하는 것 같지만
But why?
왠지
I think they know why Yuito and us are here.
유이토와 우리의 일에 대해 아는 것 같아
I don't see anything
지금 볼 수 있는 범위 내에는
within my range of sight.
의심되는 물건이나 사람이 없어
However,
하지만…
there are places I can't see.
투시하지 못하는 곳들이 아주 많아
Tsugumi, let me know if you spot anything.
츠구미, 이상한 것이 발견되면 알려줘
Leave it to me.
나한테 맡겨
Wataru, I'm counting on you too.
와타루도 잘 부탁해
The system Major General Fubuki gave us is functioning normally.
후부키 연대장님이 준비한 시스템도 문제없어
Please stay cautious.
다들 조심해
Sure.
그래
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♫A crime in reality♫
현실의 Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven's sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
거짓을 받아들여
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
영원한 환상은 점점 사라져가
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
결코 완벽하지 않아 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
뒤돌아 걸어오는 소녀는
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
순간 이 세상에 기적을 남겨
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
최고의 게임을 찾았어
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I've never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
난 언제부터 이런 세상이 질렸던 걸까
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won't be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
더는 해치고 싶지 않기에 나를 희생해
THE MOON'S SECRETS
(달의 비밀)
May I ask,
저…
what is this place?
여기는 어디인가요?
Please communicate with the history.
역사와 대화하십시오
The Moon will protect you.
달은 여러분을 지켜드릴 겁니다
Communicate? With whom?
대화라니? 누구랑 대화해?
There is no one else here except us.
우리 외에는 아무도 없어
Do they want us to read the book?
저 책을 읽으라는 건가?
Well, Tsugumi?
어때? 츠구미
I don't detect anything suspicious.
의심스러운 점은 없어
Be careful.
조심해
What is it that you seek?
무엇을 찾으십니까?
-Kyoka? -What is going on here?
-쿄카 -어떻게 된 거지?
Why is it showing Kyoka's image?
왜 쿄카가 여기에 뜨는 거야?
Name: Kyoka. Matched files: one.
이름 쿄카에 해당하는 자료가 하나 있습니다
Answering a question regarding Kyoka Eden.
쿄카 에덴에 관해 말씀드리겠습니다
Kyoka Eden.
쿄카 에덴은
She is one of the design children created by Togetsu.
토게츠에서 제작한 디자인 칠드런입니다
Design? Created?
디자인?
I had heard rumors about design children.
디자인 칠드런이라고 들어본 적 있어
I think they were created through a specific genetic combinations
내 기억이 맞는다면 특정된 유전자 조합으로
to have a certain physical appearance, strength, and brain power.
외적 특징과 신체 뇌력이 디자인된 인류야
Am I right?
맞지?
I found some information as well.
검색해봤는데
Luka's explanation is pretty much on point.
루카가 말한 것과 비슷해
It's viable theoretically,
이론상으로는 가능하지만
but it just can't work practically.
실제로는 불가능해
So Kyoka was a design child?
쿄카가 디자인 칠드런이야?
Kyoka Eden.
쿄카 에덴은
A brain power researcher.
초뇌능력 연구자인
She was created with Professor Hitoyo Pope's cells.
히토요 포프 박사님의 세포로 만들어졌습니다
Professor Pope is an expert in the field of brain power.
박사님은 뇌학과 영역의 전문가이며
She is also the founder of Togetsu Faith.
토게츠교의 교조이기도 합니다
They share the same look.
외모가 같아
Did Professor Pope make Kyoka?
그럼 포프 박사가 쿄카를 제작한 거야?
No. Professor Pope died about 2000 years ago.
아닙니다, 포프 박사님은 2000년 전에 돌아가셔서
She is no longer of this world.
이 세상에 존재하지 않습니다
She said 2000 years ago.
2000년 전?
That was about the same time New Himuka was founded.
뉴히무카 건국 시기와 같아
Maybe they have information about New Himuka from that time period.
여기에 혹시 당시의 뉴히무카에 관한 정보도 있는 걸까?
If we dig around, we might find some dirt on the government too.
잘 찾아보면 정부가 숨긴 정보를 찾아낼 수 있을지도 몰라
What was New Himuka like when it was first founded?
현재 건립된 뉴히무카는 어떤 국가이지?
Answering a question regarding the founding history of New Himuka.
뉴히무카 건국 관련 역사 개요에 대해 말씀드리겠습니다
New Himuka was founded 2020 years ago.
뉴히무카는 지금으로부터 2020년 전
It was a country founded by the people from the Ark.
선발대의 주민들이 건립한 국가입니다
The Ark? What is that?
선발대? 그게 뭐지?
It's the name of the immigrant group that moved to Earth from the Moon.
달에서 지구로 내려온 이민단의 명칭입니다
They came from the Moon?
달에서?
Yes.
네
Humans originally lived on Earth.
최초의 인류는 본래 지구에서 번식했지만
But 300 years ago,
3000년 전으로 거슬러 올라가 보면
the Earth's orbit underwent a drastic change.
지구의 궤도에 변화가 생겨
The catastrophe laid waste to Earth.
환경이 크게 변화했고
Human population was greatly reduced.
인구도 대폭으로 줄어들었습니다
For the sake of human's continuity,
종족의 존속을 위해
they moved to the Moon and built their new home.
인류는 달에 이민을 가서 도시를 건축했고
They tried to change Earth's environment from the Moon.
달 표면에서 지구의 환경을 개선했습니다
What are you talking about?
지… 지금 무슨 말을 하는 거야?
After 1000 years of effort, the rehabilitation project came to an end.
1000년을 거쳐 개선 계획도 거의 끝나가고
Earth's condition was improved to a certain degree.
지구의 환경도 어느 정도 바뀌었으니
The Moon government sent immigrants back to Earth.
달에서 이민단을 지구로 파견하였습니다
Those were people from the Ark.
그 이민단이 바로 선발대입니다
This is only getting more confusing.
뭐가 뭔지 점점 더 모르겠어
Humans moved from Earth to the Moon,
인류가 지구에서 달로 이민을 했다가
and then they returned to Earth?
다시 달에서 지구로 내려왔다고?
This is hard to believe.
그런 일이 있었어?
The immigrants from the Moon...
달에서 파견한 이민단이라
That means only a certain group of people were sent here.
즉 일부의 인류를 선택해 지구로 보냈다는 거네
Yes.
그렇습니다
Are there still people living on the Moon?
그럼 지금은 달에 인류가 있어?
I do not have a clear answer to that question.
그 질문은 정확히 답변드리기 어렵습니다
Why?
왜?
The communication with the Moon government has been completely cut off.
지금은 달 표면 정부와의 통신 라인이 전부 차단되었기 때문이죠
Cut off...
차단…
I get it now. It must be the Extinction Belt.
알겠다, 단절의 띠 때문인 거지?
Yes.
네
Due to the interference from the Extinction Belt,
단절의 띠가 준 영향으로
we have no way to know the condition on the Moon.
지금은 지구로부터 달의 상황을 얻을 수 없게 되었습니다
But if the Extinction Belt was there,
그럼 단절의 띠가 있는데
how did the immigrants get here?
이민단이 어떻게 지구에 도달한 거지?
The Extinction Belt didn't exist back then.
그때는 단절의 띠가 존재하지 않았습니다
The Extinction Belt only appeared
이민단이 지구로 내려온 뒤에
after the people came down to Earth.
단절의 띠가 나타난 건가요?
Yes, that is correct.
네, 그렇습니다
From what I know about history,
내가 배운 역사에 의하면
the Extinction Belt only appeared after the Spring of Extinction.
단절의 띠는 단절의 봄 때문에 나타났는데
The Spring of Extinction happened during the founding era.
그리고 단절의 봄은 건국 시기에 발생했지
So the Others and the Extinction belt showed up around the same time?
괴이가 단절의 띠와 함께 나타난 거야?
No, the Others came some time
아닙니다, 단절의 띠가 나타난 뒤
after the Extinction Belt appeared.
한참 지나고 나타난 겁니다
They didn't appear together?
함께 나타난 것이 아니라고?
But the Others came from the Extinction Belt.
하지만 괴이는 단절의 띠에서 나온 거잖아
What do you make of this?
네 생각은 어때?
This is a little hard to believe.
믿어지지 않아
The Others...
괴이…
What exactly are the Others?
괴이가 대체 뭐야?
I do not possess the information
그 문제에 관해서는
to answer that question.
당신이 원하는 정보가 없습니다
You require access to BABE.
베이브에 진입하셔야 합니다
BABE?
베이브?
Is there another system similar to this?
다른 시스템도 있는 거야?
We got information Suoh and Seiran government don't have.
스오와 세이란에서 얻을 수 없었던 정보이긴 한데
I gave up halfway through the explanation.
난 반쯤 듣고 이해하는 걸 포기했어
The information is simply unbelievable.
너무 터무니없는 얘기야
We should only take it as a verbal legend passed down in Togetsu.
토게츠에서 전해지는 전설 같은 거겠지
Maybe it's part of the Togetsu Faith's scripture.
토게츠교 교전 중의 일부분이 아닐까?
If the immigrants founded New Himuka...
이민단이 뉴히무카를 만든 거라면
So our founding father, Yakumo Sumeragi, came from the Moon too.
건국자인 야쿠모 스메라기도 달에서 왔다는 얘기잖아?
It's just as the hologram said.
영상에서 한 말이 사실이라면
It's not just Yuito, but the whole human population on Earth.
유이토 뿐만 아니라 모든 지구인이
We are all descendants of the immigrants from the Moon.
달에서 온 이민단의 후대인 거지
That can't be real.
그럴 리가 없잖아
I know.
그러니까
Try asking something else.
다른 것도 물어보자
Please tell us what you know about the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트에 관한 정보를 알려줘
A question regarding the Kunad Gate.
쿠나도 게이트에 관해 말씀드리겠습니다
Kunad Gate: A black hole that appeared above the Kunad Highway.
쿠나도 게이트는 쿠나도 고속도로에 나타난 블랙홀 같은 현상인데요
It's gravitational pull is abnormal and still growing.
중력 이상 사태가 점점 더 심해져
It will consume the whole planet soon.
머지않은 미래에는 지구를 삼킬 것이며
Due to Yuito Sumeragi's brain power,
또한 유이토 스메라기의 초뇌능력 영향으로
the Kunad Gate is still growing.
쿠나도 게이트가 점점 확대되고 있습니다
Earth's total destruction is inevitable.
지구의 멸망은 이제 피할 수 없게 되었습니다
How is Yuito part of this?
유이토 얘기가 여기서 왜 나와?
However, you need not fear.
하지만 겁내실 필요 없습니다
Place your faith in Togetsu,
토게츠교만 믿으신다면
everyone will be granted salvation.
모든 이가 구원을 얻을 수 있을 겁니다
The Moon will protect all of you.
달이 여러분을 지켜드릴 거니까요
Wait! How is my power affecting the Kunad Gate?
잠깐만, 내 초뇌능력이 왜?
What does it have to do with me?
쿠나도 게이트와 내가 어떤 연관이 있는 거야?
The Kunad Gate is correcting trivial matters
쿠나도 게이트는 사소한 문제를 교정하고
and bringing the flawed universe back to the right path.
잘못된 우주를 바로잡아
It's the very phenomenon that will bring the righteous future.
정확한 미래를 실현할 것이며
The souls marching toward death
사망에 이르는 영혼은
will return to the Moon.
달로 되돌아갈 것입니다
Yuito, don't be concerned about the story.
유이토, 방금 그거 신경 쓰지 마
But the Kunad Gate is indeed consuming its surrounding.
쿠나도 게이트가 주위 물체를 흡수하는 건 사실이지만
Will it grow to the point where it consumes Earth?
진짜 점점 더 커져서 결국 지구를 삼키게 되는 걸까?
We shouldn't believe those stories.
너무 믿으면 안 될 것 같아
Yes. It might be a trap.
그래, 함정일 수도 있어
We mustn't be tricked.
다 믿으면 안 돼
You have a point.
하긴 그래
So, what shall we do next?
그럼 이제 어떻게 할까?
I'm concerned with the system named BABE.
난 아까 말한 '베이브'가 신경 쓰여
When we asked her about the Others,
괴이에 관한 질문을 하니까
she said we'd require access to BABE.
'베이브'에 진입해야 한다고 했어
Do you seek the knowledge of BABE?
'베이브'에 관한 정보가 필요하십니까?
What is BABE?
'베이브'가 뭐죠?
It's the city computer that manages Togetsu.
토게츠를 관리하는 도시 컴퓨터입니다
So it functions like Suoh's Arahabaki.
스오의 아라하바키 같은 건가?
Togetsu has a management system too?
토게츠에도 있네
I'll lead the way, please follow me.
길을 안내해드리겠습니다, 이쪽으로 오시죠
Kasane, answer me!
카사네, 어서 대답해
Arashi? Kagero?
아라시, 카게로
We fell for Kyoka's trick.
쿄카 누님한테 한 방 먹은 건가?
Please answer me! Kyoka! Shiden!
제발, 쿄카, 시덴, 얼른 대답해
What happened to everyone?
다들 어떻게 된 거야?
I'll be right back.
잠시 다녀올게
The memories we share
두 사람과 함께한 시간이
will not perish.
그냥 이대로 사라지지 않을 거야
There are two brains controlling the Red Strings.
레드 스트링스를 조종할 대뇌는 두 개다
We'll reach our goal very soon.
곧 우리가 원하던 성과를 얻을 수 있겠어
Huh?
어라?
Shiden, aren't you coming with us?
시덴은 안 따라와?
Kasane, you still lack the resolve.
카사네, 넌 아직 각오가 안 돼 있어
We are just the same.
우리도 마찬가지고
Thank you.
고마워
I'm doing this to correct this flawed world.
전부 잘못된 우주를 바로잡기 위해서야
Sorry, but I need to borrow this.
미안, 잠깐만 빌려 쓸게
Yuito and Tsugumi...
유이토와 츠구미잖아?
Kasane...
카사네…
Who is it?
누구야
Someone is beckoning me.
누가 날 부르는 거야?
Kasane, congratulations. You're finally awake.
카사네, 깨어난 걸 축하해
Kasane...
카사네…
Look.
이거 봐
The puppy is small like you are.
카사네마냥 귀여운 강아지야
Look at it barking. Don't you find it adorable?
멍멍대는 모습이 귀엽지?
A puppy?
강아지?
I feel this nostalgia, but why?
왜 이렇게 그리운 느낌이지?
I know this person.
난… 이 사람을 알아
It was killed.
살해되었어
Yes, I remember.
그래, 기억나
My precious friend was murdered right before me.
제일 소중했던 친구가 내 앞에서…
The data is the same.
수치 변동이 없다
That didn't trigger her brain power.
초뇌능력이 발동되지 않았다
Killing her beloved animal doesn't bring enough stimuli to her.
애완견의 죽음이 자극적이지 않은가 보다…
That's enough!
그만 해요
Stop hurting this poor child's soul!
더는… 카사네의 어린 마음에 상처 주지 말라고요
Is this really for the sake of our future?
진짜 미래를 위한 일이 맞습니까?
She is a Design Child created for this exact purpose.
그 아이는 그러기 위해 태어난 디자인 칠드런이다
She is unlike the failure you are.
실패한 너와는 다르다
For the sake of correcting this universe,
잘못된 우주를 바로잡고
to secure the real future,
정확한 미래를 얻기 위해서는
we need the Red Strings.
레드 스트링스가 필요하다
Is there a need to do so?
진짜 교정할 필요가 있는 겁니까?
Mother. It was so warm and gentle.
엄마는 따뜻하고 부드럽고
She was always trying to protect me.
늘 나를 지켜주는 사람이었다
But I lost the memories.
그런데 난 잊고 있었다…
Is there a need to correct the world?
진짜 교정할 필요가 있는 거냐고요
The world is great as it is now!
지금 세상도 나쁘지 않잖아요
No, what is this sensation?
싫어… 이 느낌은 뭐지?
I don't want to remember this.
생각하기 싫어
The outcome of your failed education is beyond disappointing.
교육 실패로 이 지경까지 이르다니
We only assigned you as her caretaker so you'd have something to do.
무용지물인 너에게 아이를 지키라 했더니…
Yes. That's enough.
그러게, 이제 필요 없어졌어
We'll proceed with her.
이번에는 이 여자로 하지
Yes.
그래…
Is that so?
그런가요…?
So you...
당신들은 역시…
All of you...
이놈들이…
My mother was...
엄마를…
Kasane, I'm sorry.
카사네, 미안해
I wish you a great future.
너의 미래는 행복했으면 좋겠어
Yes.
그래
I lost my caretaker that very day.
그날… 나를 지켜주었던 사람
I lost my mother.
엄마를 잃었어
I was created as a brain power user.
난 창조된 초뇌능력자였어
The power of the Red Strings...
이 힘, 레드 스트링스가
Where am I?
여기는…
The memories I forgot.
잊고 지냈던 기억들
I...
난…
Kasane.
카사네…
Stop hurting this poor child's soul!
더는… 카사네의 어린 마음에 상처 주지 말라고요
Mother...
엄마…
CONTACT LOST
(연결 불가)
Damn it!
젠장
You can stop trying now, Shiden.
이제 그만 포기하지, 시덴
What?
뭐?
You're too noisy, I can't sleep.
시끄러워 죽겠네, 잠 좀 자자
How can you still sleep in this situation?
이런 상황에 잠이 와?
Panicking won't do us any good.
어쩔 수 없잖아
We should rest while we can.
쉴 수 있을 때 쉬어야 하지 않겠어?
You should get some sleep too.
너도 좀 쉬어
As if I can sleep!
잠이 올 리가 없잖아
Kyoka.
쿄카
Even you...
너마저…
Lady Kasane, we brought you new clothes.
쿄카 님, 새로운 옷을 가져왔습니다
-What is it? -Verify it now.
-왜 그래? -얼른 확인해
Wait, it's me.
잠깐만, 나야
Kagero.
카게로
The dashing prince is here to save his princess.
갇혀있는 공주님을 구하러 온 왕자님이라고
My lady, please don't punch me in the face.
공주가 왕자님한테 주먹 날리면 안 되지
You left the team before we even entered Togetsu.
우리가 토게츠에 진입하기 전에 넌 소대를 이탈했어
Did you know?
설마 너 그때 이미…
If I were in cahoot with Kyoka,
내가 쿄카와 한패인지 묻고 싶은 거지?
why would I come here to rescue you?
그럼 널 구하러 왜 왔겠어?
Calm down and think.
침착하게 잘 생각해봐
I told you so, didn't I?
내가 말했지?
You'd regret coming to Togetsu.
토게츠에 온 걸 후회하게 될 거라고
I'll explain everything to you later.
나중에 다시 설명할게
This place has become far worse after I left.
토게츠는 내가 지냈던 그때보다 훨씬 엉망이야
I think they got their hands on something.
그리고 이놈들이 뭔가 잡은 것 같아
Yuito and his team are here too.
유이토 일행도 왔거든
Yuito is here too? This is bad.
유이토? 큰일이야
Togetsu is after my Red Strings.
토게츠의 목표가 내 레드 스트링스니까
Yuito probably has the same power as mine.
나와 비슷한 힘을 가진 유이토도…
I thought as much.
그런 것 같아
It seems I have no choice but to save them too.
그 자식들도 구해야겠네
Let's get moving.
얼른 움직이자
Lady Kasane isn't here.
카사네 님이 사라졌어
Kasane went missing?
카사네가 사라졌다고?
It's not fun to meet the people
토게츠 녀석들은
from Togetsu.
너무 재미없어
Well, that's it for me.
뭐, 그냥 그렇다고
Hey! Come back!
어이, 잠깐만
Kagero...
카게로…
Kasane! Kagero!
카사네, 카게로
Thank goodness you two are safe.
다행이다, 괜찮은 거야?
Haruka, where is Arashi and the team?
하루카, 아라시 일행은?
I don't know, I can't contact them.
모르겠어, 연락이 안 돼
You knew they'd be captured.
어디에 갇혀있는지 알아?
What a shame.
아쉽게도…
I know where Yuito is.
유이토 일행이 어디로 가는지 알겠어
Master Yuito, this is the place.
유이토 님, 바로 이곳입니다
BABE will answer all of your questions.
베이브는 모든 질문에 대답할 것입니다
Master Yuito, I'm sure you want to know whether the information was true or falsified.
유이토 님은 분명 조금 전에 들은 정보가 사실인지 궁금하시겠죠
A conversation with BABE will clear your doubts.
베이브와 소통하면 반드시 의혹을 잠재우실 수 있을 겁니다
Please, verify it yourself.
잘 확인하시기 바랍니다
The Moon will protect you.
달이 여러분을 지켜드릴 거니까요
This is too suspicious no matter how you see it.
아무리 생각해봐도 이상해
We wouldn't let any outsider gain access to the mainframe of Arahabaki.
외부인은 보통 아라하바키 같은 시스템에 진입할 수 없잖아
This is too baffling.
진짜 말도 안 돼
Why would a religious group need this powerful computer?
이렇게 작은 종교단체에 아라하바키와 같은 컴퓨터가 필요할까?
Wataru, can you hear me?
와타루… 들려?
No, we lost the psynet connection.
안돼, 사이넷과 연결이 끊겼어
We must leave at once as soon as we get the information.
필요한 정보만 찾고 얼른 떠나자
Yes.
그래
What? Isn't some hologram going to show up?
이상하네, 왜 아무도 안 나타나는 거야?
What's going on?
뭐지?
ALERT
(경고)
This feeling...
이 느낌…
It feels like the connection to SAS!
SAS와 연결할 때랑 느낌이 같아
Yuito...
유이토
This is bad.
큰일이야…
I can't move my body.
몸이… 말을 안 들어
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
운명의 지시 따윈 필요 없어
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
분명 고쳐질 거라 믿으니까
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
앞으로도 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 말이야
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
눈부시게 빛나는 태양이 막을 내리고
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
세상의 끝에서 뭘 기다리고 있는걸까
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
♫Who can shake us♫
누가 우리를 위협해
♫Who can define us♫
누가 우리 대신 결정해
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
이건 우리만의 스토리야
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
네 마음속 미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
DESIGN CHILDREN
(디자인 칠드런)